<menu>
	 <disease><!--Cardiovascular system-->
		 <name>Hypertension</name>
		 <symptoms>
			headache, shortness of breath, nosebleed
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Lifestyle modification.
			2.Salt restriction.
			3.Weight loss.
			4.beta-blocker (atenolol, metoprolol).
			5.Calcium channel blockers (amlodipine) alone or in combination.
			6.Thiazide diuretics.
			7.ACE inhibitors: enalapril, lisinoprilm ramipril.
			8.Angiotensin receptor blockers: losartan, telmisartan.

		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--Cardiovascular system-->
		 <name>Ischaemic Heart Disease</name>
		 <symptoms>
			shortness of breath, chest pain, extreme fatigue, fainting, heart palpitation, weight gain, difficulty sleeping,
			swelling in leg feet abdomen, cough, congestion
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.short-and long-acting nitrates.
			2.beta-adrenergic blockers.
			3.calcium channel antagonists.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--Cardiovascular system-->
		 <name>Acute Myocardial Infarction</name>
		 <symptoms>
			anxiety, cough, dizziness, fast heart rate, heaviness in chest, chest pain, shortness of breath,
			sweating, vomiting
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Angiotensin-converting enzyme (ACE) inhibitors.
			2.Angiotensin receptor blockers (ARBs).
			3.Anti-ischemic agents such as ranolazine (Ranexa).
			4.Beta-blockers.
			5.Calcium channel blockers.
			6.Nitrates.
			7.Statins.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Chronic Cardiac Failure</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Anxiety, restlessness unresponsiveness,
			delirium, lethargy, hallucinations
			Chest pain, chest tightness, heart palpitations,
			Dizziness, Extreme Fatigue, blood-tinged phlegm, 
			cyanosis, shortness of breath, labored breathing, wheezing, choking.
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Lifestyle and dietary changes to maintain an ideal weight and fitness level. 
			2.Consume low saturated fat, trans fats, and sodium.
			3.ACE inhibitors (ramipril, lisinopril, enalapril, captopril).
			4.Aldosterone blockers (Aldactone).
			5.Anticoagulants (aspirin, Coumadin, Plavix).
			6.Beta-blockers (metoprolol, atenolol and propranolol).
			7.Cholesterol-lowering medications (statins).
			8.Digitalis drugs (digoxin).
			9.Diuretics (Lasix, Bumex, HCTZ).
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Orthostatic Hypotension	</name>
		 <symptoms>
			faintness on standing, frequent fall, dizziness, neck pain, syncope,
			weakness in limbs on standing, micturition syncopesm
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Take rest.
			2.Stop drugs like antihypertensives, diuretics, tricyclic antidepressants.
			3.Do not give vain therapy to normalize blood pressure.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Syncope</name>
		 <symptoms>
			transient loss of consciousness, Disorientation, Irregular heart beat, 
			Slow heart rate (bradycardia), fainting, Headache
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Medications (antidepressants and blood pressure drugs).
			2.Prevent pooling of blood in the legs.
			3.Surgical procedures (insertion of a pacemaker).
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--respiratory system--><!--Smoking is the single most important cause of respiratory disease in old age-->
		 <name>Pneumonia</name>
		 <symptoms>
			confusion, incontinence, immobility, fever
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Antibiotic medications. 
			2.Bronchodilators.
			3.Cool-mist vaporizer
			4.Drink plenty of fluids to prevent dehydration.
			5.Medications to relieve fever and body aches.
			6.Oxygen therapy help relieve shortness of breath..
			7.Take proper Rest.
			8.Thick phlegm may need to be medically suctioned.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Tuberculosis</name>
		 <symptoms>
			fever, night sweats, haemoptysis, cough, weight loss 
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.A short course chemotherapeutic regimen, unsupervised or directly observed,
			with isoniazid (5mg/kg/day), rifampicin (10mg/kg/day), ethambutol (15mg/kg/day) and pyrazinamide (25mg/kg/day)
			or treptomucin (0.5 g/day) for two months followed by isoniazed and rifampicin for four months.
			2.Avoid streptomycin.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Bronchial Asthma</name>
		 <symptoms>
			intermittent cough, wheezing, breathlessness, cough, chest tightness
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Diagnose asthma if you find wheeze with dyspnoea in the absence of a history of smoking.
			2.Acute asthma should be managed with high-flow oxygen and nebulized beta-agonists and ipratropium.
			3.Treat with intravenous aminophylline and salbutamol patient not respond to above.
			4.Patients with rising carbon dioxide retention and impending exhaustion should be managed with mechanical ventilation.
			5.Chronic bronchial asthma is managed with metered dose inhalers (MDI) of beta-agonists (salbutamol or terbutaline), 
			steroid (beclomethasone or budesonide) and ipratropium. 
			6.Chronic severe bronchial asthma requires oral corticosteroids (prednisolone) with its accompanying verse effects.
			7.15% improvement in FEV after salbutamol nebulization indicates a diagnosis of asthma.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease</name>
		 <symptoms>
			hypoxia, fatigue, malaise, weight loss, Difficulty in sleeping, 
			hyperinflated chest, wheezing, 
			cyanosis, oedema, raise in jvp.
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Relief of airway obstruction by Bronchodilators  beta-agonists (salbutamol, terburaline) oral and inhaled anticholinergic inhaler (ipratropium).
			2.Steroid inhalers (beclomethasone, budesonide).
			3.Theophylline.
			4.Long-term home oxygen therapy is recommended in patients with persistent hypoxia (PO2 less than 55) for minimum 16 hours per day.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Lung cancer</name>
		 <symptoms>
			cough, haemoptysis, chest pain, weight loss
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Radical or palliative radiotherapy. 
			2.Chemotherapy is mostly reserved for small cell cancer and is poorly tolerated.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--endocrine system-->
		 <name>Diabetes Mellitus</name>
		 <symptoms>
		 <!-- type 1-->
			weight loss,
			extreme fatigue, 
			mood changes,
			Flu-Like Symptoms,
			Vomiting,
			<!-- type 2-->
			erectile dysfunction (ED),
			Frequent infections,
			Odd sensations, 
			Weakness,
		<!--Serious Condition-->
			Abdominal pain,
			Confusion,
			Dry skin or mouth,
			Fruity smelling breath,
			Severe thirst and frequent urination,
			Shortness of breath,
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Venous plasma glucose level of 200 mg after two hours of 75 g of oral glucose.
			2.Insulin sensitizing drugs such as metaformin, pioglitazone.	
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--endocrinesystem-->
		 <name>HypoThyroidism</name>
		 <symptoms>
			obesity, deafness, cold intolerance, fatigue, course skin, low cardiac output state
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Replacement of l-thyroxine.
			2.High TSH with low t3 and t4 concentration
			start with low dose(0.025 mg) and increase slowly to avoid cardiovascular toxicity.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--endocrinesystem-->
		 <name>HyperThyroidism</name>
		 <symptoms>
			progressive functional decline, anorrexia, weight loss, fatigue, cardiac arrythymia, cardiac failure
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Thyroid scan.
			2.Beta blockers to  minimize rapid heart rate and anxiety.
			3.Antithyroid medications, In some cases antithyroid medications may cure hyperthyroidism.
			4.Surgery to remove the overactive thyroid gland may be performed. This can cure the disorder.
			5.Swallowing of radioactive iodine.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--urinarysystem-->
		 <name>Urinary Tract Infection</name>
		 <symptoms>
			burning stinging pain,cloudy bloody urine, Frequent urge to urinate, leaking urine, pressure or pain in your pelvic area or lower belly
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Five to seven day course of therapy with amoxicillin, cotrimoxazole, norfloxacin or ciprofloxacin is effective.
			2.In the presence of shock and septicaemia, parenteral antibiotic therapy with ciprofloxacin, cephalosporins or aminoglycosides and hospitalization are required.
			3.Drink plenty of fluids.
		</diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Benign Prostatic Hypertrophy</name>
		 <symptoms>
			hesitancy and straining starting a urine stream, weak flow of the urine stream, Dribbling after urination,
			Feeling that the bladder is not completely empty, urge to urinate again soon after urinating,
			Pain during urination (dysuria)
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Till recently surgery, initially abdominal and later transurethral, was the only mode of therapy
			for prostatic hypertrophy.
			2.In recent years medical management with specific long acting beta1- adrenergic antagonists
			(such as terazosin 2.5-5 mg, dozaxosin 2-4 mg, tamsulosin 0.4mg) have been used with excellent results.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Malignancy Of Prostate</name>
		 <symptoms>
			In early stage-
			hesitancy and straining starting a urine stream, weak flow of the urine stream, Dribbling after urination,
			Feeling that the bladder is not completely empty, urge to urinate again soon after urinating,
			Pain during urination (dysuria),
			in last stage-skeletal metastatic disease is common
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Radical surgery in early stages.
			2.Hormonal manipulation with anti-androgens, namely, non-steroidal flutamide and
			steroidal diethylstilboesterol have been found to be effective when combined with bilateral orchidectomy.
			3.Radiotherapy is another alternative in such patients.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Urinary Incontinence</name>
		 <symptoms>
			A sudden urgent need to urinate,
			Sudden leakage of urine,
			The need to urinate frequently,
			A feeling of fullness in the bladder even after urination,
			Leakage of urine while sleeping,
			A urine stream that stops and restarts during urination,
			Difficulty urinating even while feeling the urge to urinate
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Exercises to strengthen the pelvic floor muscles.
			2.Avoid spicy foods, caffeine, and carbonated drinks.
			3.Anticholinergics/antimuscarinics (Detrol, Ditropan XL, Enablex, Oxytrol, Urispas, and Vesicare) can prevent bladder spasms.
			4.Oxytrol, Detrol, Ditropan XL, Myrbetriq, and Vesicare also are approved for women with overactive bladder (OAB).
			5.If the above treatments don't provide enough relief, surgery may help. 
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--mental health system-->
		 <name>Depression</name>
		 <symptoms>
			somatic complaints, sleep disturbance and agitation, anorexia, thoughts of death, 
			impaired concentration and dysphoria, Cognitive impairment
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Antidepressants are effective in old age.
			2.Therapeutic doses of tricyclic antidepressants and serotonin re-uptake inhibitors 
			(fluoxetine 20-40 mg once daily, sertraline 25-50 mg once daily).
			3.Lithium is also effective in old age despite an increased risk of nephrotoxicity.
			4.Electroconvulsive therapy (ECTY) is safe in old age with more than 60% recovery rate.
			5.Psychotherapy is useful in depression in old age.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--neurological system-->
		 <name>Parkinson Disease</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Rhytmcim tremor, Fixed posture, Monotonous voice, Tendency to fall, Rigidity, Mask-like face, 
			Difficulty in initiating movement, Freezing episodes, Festinating gait, Loss of arm swing, 
			Sleep disturbances, Psychosis, Depression, Dementia in late stages
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Enhancement of dopaminergic transmission In the brain by oral drugs such as levodopa, bromocriptine and selegiline.
			2.Use of anticholinergic drugs also improves symptoms and functionality.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Stroke</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Sudden weakness or numbness in the face, arm, or leg on one side of the body,
			Abrupt loss of vision, strength, coordination, sensation, speech, or the ability to understand speech,
			Sudden dimness of vision, especially in one eye,
			Sudden loss of balance, possibly accompanied by vomiting, nausea, fever, hiccups, or trouble with swallowing,
			Sudden and severe headache with no other cause followed rapidly by loss of consciousness -- indications of a stroke due to bleeding,
			Brief loss of consciousness,
			Unexplained dizziness or sudden falls
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Call for instant medical assistance.
			2.Give a clot-dissolving medicine called tissue plasminogen activator (t-PA).
			3.You may also receive aspirin or another antiplatelet medicine.
			4.Control bleeding, reduce pressure in the brain, and stabilize vital signs, especially blood pressure.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--sensory system-->
		 <name>Cataract</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Frequent changes in eyeglasses, Needing brighter light to read,
			Poor night vision, Fading or yellowing of colours.
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Treatment of cataract is generally surgical which depends on the patient&apos;s visual needs. 
			2.Prescription for glass has now been replaced by implantation of intraocular lens, which restores near normal focusing ability.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Glaucoma</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Abnormal pupil size, nonreactivity to light,Glare or halos around lights, 
			Increased sensitivity to light, Poor night vision, Red eye, 
			Seeing floating objects in your vision, Swelling of eyes
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Eye drops for glaucoma.
			2.Laser surgery for glaucoma.
			3.Microsurgery for glaucoma.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Skin Infection</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Red skin, Itchy skin, Rashes
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.For better treatment consult immediately to a dermatologist.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--musculoskeletal system-->
		 <name>Osteoarthritis</name>
		 <symptoms>
			pain, stiffness, bone sweeling, loss of movement, instability
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Acetaminophen (Tylenol) to relieve pain.
			2.Cortisone injection to reduce inflammation.
			3.Glucosamine and chondroitin to strengthen damaged joint cartilage.
			4.Injection of a synovial fluid substitute to help lubricate joints and ease stiffness and movement.
			5.Nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs), such as ibuprofen (Advil, Motrin) and aspirin to reduce inflammaion.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Rheumatoid Arthritis</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Stiffness, Redness, swelling, tenderness or pain, Limited motion, Loss of energy or fatigue, Low-grade fever,
			Loss of appetite
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs), such as ibuprofen, can be used to quickly ease swelling, stiffness and pain.
			2.Corticosteroid drugs, such as prednisone, may also be used for quick relief. Corticosteroids may put you at greater risk for osteoporosis (bone weakness).
			3.Methotrexate, chloroquine is used for long-term relief of RA. It is called a disease-modifying anti-rheumatic drug (DMARD).
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Osteoporosis</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Back pain due to spinal bone fractures, Bone pain or tenderness, Fracture that occurs with little or no trauma,
			Loss of height, Neck pain due to spinal bone fractures, Stooped posture (spine curvature, kyphosis)
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Following a diet containing sufficient amounts of calcium and vitamin D.
			2.Bisphosphonates, such as alendronate (Fosamax), and risedronate (Actonel), to decrease bone loss and to increase bone density.
			3.Calcitonin, which can slow the rate of bone loss and help minimize pain.
			4.Raloxifene (Evista), which is used to prevent and treat osteoporosis in postmenopausal women and
			which can make bones stronger and reduce the risk of fractures.
			5.Teriparatide (Forteo), which contains parathyroid hormone and encourages new bone tissue growth and reduces the risk of fractures.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--Brain Disease and cognitive impairment system-->
		 <name>Dementia</name>
		 <symptoms>
			 Changes in mood, change in personality or behavior, Changes in sleep pattern, Confusion,Difficulty performing complex tasks 
			 , Difficulty with memory thinking talking comprehension writing or reading, Impaired reasoning,
			 Impaired spatial ability and orientation, Loss of judgment, Social withdrawal
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Cholinesterase inhibitors, such as donepezil (Aricept), galantamine (Razadyne), and rivastigmine (Exelon) to
			increase the availability of a chemical that is required for nerve signaling in the brain.
			2.NMDA receptor antagonists such as memantine (Namenda) to decrease the overexcitement of certain receptors
			in the brain that may contribute to the degenerative process.
			3.Antianxiety medications such as buspirone (Buspar)
			4.Antidepressants, such as citalopram (Celexa), fluoxetine (Prozac), imipramine (Tofranil), and trazodone (Desyrel), to help stabilize moods.
			5.Antipsychotics, such as haloperidol (Haldol), olanzapine (Zyprexa), and risperidone (Risperdal), for severe behavioral issues.
			6.Stimulants such as methylphenidate (Methylin, Ritalin) to improve sleep disorders and flat moods.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Alzheimer</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Disorders of languages, Bedboundness and mutism, Increased forgetfullness,
			Disorientation, Decreased problem solving, Anorexia
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Aricept is the only treatment for all stages of Alzheimer&apos;s disease: mild, moderate, and severe.
			2.Razadyne (formerly called Reminyl) is also for mild to moderate Alzheimer&apos;s. 
			3.Exelon is for people who have mild to moderate Alzheimer&apos;s. 
			4.Memantine (Namenda)treats moderate-to-severe Alzheimer&apos;s disease.Namenda&apos;s side effects
			  include tiredness, dizziness, confusion, constipation, and headache.
			5.Namzaric This drug is a mix of Namenda and Aricept. It's best for people with moderate to severe Alzheimer&apos;s
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Vascular Dementia</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Vision loss, Disorientation, Loss of abilit to understand speech, Confusion
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Lifestyle changes like following a low-salt diet to manage high blood pressure,
			losing weight if overweight,stopping smoking if you smoke, cutting down on alcohol 
			reduce your risk of experiencing further damage to your brain.
			2.ACE inhibitors and beta-blockers, to treat high blood pressure
			3.Statins to treat high cholesterol
			4.Antiplatelets, such as aspirin or clopidogrel, to reduce the risk of blood clots and further strokes
			5.Anticoagulants, such as warfarin, which can also reduce your risk of blood clots and further strokes
			6.Diabetes medication, such as metformin
			7.Antidepressants to treat depression
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Confusion/Delirium</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Incontinence, Hallucination, Disorganised thinking, Memory loss, Confusion, Disorientation
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Treatment depends on the condition causing delirium. So, better to consult a doctor.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease><!--Gastrointestinal system-->
		 <name>Hiatus Hernia &amp; Gastroesophageal Reflux</name>
		 <symptoms>
			heartburn, dysphagia, pain in lower sternum, belching, reflux of food, vomiting
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Weight loss if overweight.
			2.Proper diet.
			3.Avoid tea, coffee and colas.
			4.Reduced use of saturated fat.
			5.Take antacis/skimmed milk for heartburn.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>NSAID Gastropathy &amp; peptic ulcer</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Black colored stool, Anorexia, Weigth loss, Blood in vomit, Nausea, Abdominal pain
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Stop taking NSAIDs.
			2.Proton pump inhibitors (PPIs) (such as Prilosec).
			3.H2 blockers (such as Zantac).
			4.Prostaglandin analogs (such as Cytotec).
			5.Antacids (such as Tums).
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Non Ulcer Dyspepsia</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Abdominal pain, Bloating, Nausea, Indigestion
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.If you are infected with H. pylori, the first treatment usually tried is to clear the H. pylori infection.
			2.Acid-suppressing medicines like proton pump inhibitors (PPIs) and H2-receptor antagonists. 
			3.PPIs include omeprazole, lansoprazole, pantoprazole, rabeprazole and esomeprazole.
			4.H2-receptor antagonists include cimetidine, famotidine, nizatidine and ranitidine. 
			5.Lifestyle changes includes eat regular meals. Lose weight, if you are obese.
			If you are a smoker, consider giving up. Don't drink too much alcohol.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Cancer of GI tract</name>
		 <symptoms>
			New onset of constipation, Loss of appetite, Change in bowel habits, Dell pain radiationg to 
			back, Weakness, Weight loss, Blood in stool
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			Perform Imaging studies and tests to examine the blood and urine to detect
			and diagnose gastrointestinal carcinoid tumors. Based on tumor give one of following treatment
			1.Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer Treatment.
			2.Pancreatic Neuroendocrine Tumors (Islet Cell Tumors) Treatment.
			3.Rectal Cancer Treatment.
			4.Small Intestine Cancer Treatment.
			5.Unusual Cancers of Childhood Treatment
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Constipation</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Straining during bowel movement, Stomach ache, No bowel movement in 3 days,
			Diarrhoea like stool, Hard compacted stool, Blood in stool
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.Consume more fiber in your diet.
			2.Take mild laxatives.
			3.For stubborn constipation doctor may recommend a non-digestible sugar called lactulose. 
			4.Lubiprostone (Amitiza) and linaclotide (Linzess) for long-term use in chronic constipation in adults and the elderly.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
	 
	 <disease>
		 <name>Cancer</name>
		 <symptoms>
			Fatigue,
			Lump or area of thickening under the skin,
			Weight changes including unintended loss or gain,
			Skin changes such as yellowing, darkening or redness of the skin, sores that won't heal, or changes to existing moles,
			Changes in bowel or bladder habits,
			Persistent cough or trouble breathing,
			Difficulty swallowing,
			Hoarseness,
			Persistent indigestion or discomfort after eating,
			Persistent, unexplained muscle or joint pain,
			Persistent, unexplained fevers or night sweats,
			Unexplained bleeding or bruising.
		 </symptoms>
		 <diagnosis>
			1.In case of any mentioned symptoms immediateliiy consult the Doctors.
			2.Various tests are there such as Physiacal tests, Laboratory tests, Imaging tests and Biopsy.
			3.In case of Cancer, Together you and your doctor can weigh the benefits and risks of
			each cancer treatment to determine which is best for you. Treatments are-
			Surgery, Chemotherapy, Radiation therapy, Stem cell transplant, Immunotherapy, Hormone Therapy.
		 </diagnosis>
	 </disease>
  
	 
	 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
</menu>